Neighbors, Inc. 110 110
Stage
- Series 1
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Misc. items, January 1977-October 1979 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Public hearings, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Volunteers, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Address Labels, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Apartment house list, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Blair road Block org., Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tuckerman Block organization, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Block representation, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Block spotters information and reports, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Block Steering Committee, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Old Board of Directors list, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Shepherd Park, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Brightwood, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Brightwood, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Community Organizers reports, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Community Organizers reports, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Block captain and groups, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Block organization information, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer forms, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Survey questionnaires, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Volunteers Committee, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Colonial Village, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Garden Club Activities, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Congressional letter re housing, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Housing, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Ford Foundation Proposals and correspondence, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Landlord/Tenant rights, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Block meetings, invitations to, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Membership Drives, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Nominating Committee, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Open house guest lists, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Organization address lists, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Printing services information, Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Service area system map and information, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Social programs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Manor Park Canvassers lists, Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Fair Housing - Assessments, Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Fair Housing - Communication from other groups, Undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Fair Housing - Department of Housing and Community Development, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Fair Housing - Statement, Undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Fair Housing - Rent strikes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Fair Housing - Block leadership and programs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Fair Housing - House for V.P., Undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Fair Housing - Housing regulations, Undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Fair Housing - Lewis and Silverman, Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Fair Housing - Housing Committees, Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Fair Housing - Housing Committees, Undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Fair Housing - Housing Committees, Undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - National Neighbors Newsletter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Parkside apartments, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Preferred realtors info, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Realtors, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Real estate housing, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Housing information, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Housing Opportunities Council, MOCO, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Contribution and Pledge cards, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ads, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - American Democracy In Action, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 10th Caberet, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - City Regulations Committee, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Tax Reform in D.C., Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Community Singers, Inc., Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Budget Office (D.C.), Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - House District Committee, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Board of Commissioners (D.C.), Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Legislative Council, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - D.C. City council meeting information, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Sales tax, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Education Committee, 1962, 1963-1964, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Title III, University of Maryland plan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Education Committee reports, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - IED end of year evaluation, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - False reports, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Housing ideas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Housing and community development, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Forum and earlier, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Housing Information service, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Housing Opportunities Council, Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Legislation, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Legislative, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Services Traffic, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Pre-School Education Committee, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Proposed priorities for 1976-77, Randy Kinder, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Public Schools, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Public Schools, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Quotations and speech material, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Real estate committee, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Real estate, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - School leaflet, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - School board elections, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - School materials, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Shepherd Park school questions, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Suggestions for 1970 reorganization, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Parent Questionnaires, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Reprints and publications, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Takoma Library, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Takoma Elementary School Ed. Comm., Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Takoma School Proposal, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Washington, D.C. City Council, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Water Fund Thank You letter, Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Waterline [various subtopics] (7 files), Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Govt. Misc., Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Commissions on Human Relations, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Complaints for Action referrals to Neighborhood services, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Cleanup campaign, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - D.C. school board reports, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Coolidge High School, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Education, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Education - Ad Hoc Coalition, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Education - Hobson v. Hansen, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Education - Board of Education Minutes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Education - Passow Study Subcommittee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Education - Takoma Elementary School Replacement, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Job applicants, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Personnel material, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - IED, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - IED, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Unsuccessful candidates for Executive Director, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Real estate survey, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Press releases and publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer reports, Undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Board of Director meeting minutes, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Agendas, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Annual report, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Annual reports and meetings, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Board of Director meeting minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Membership summary reports, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Membership, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Monthly reports, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer reports and budgets, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Board meetings, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - NI area maps, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Shepherd Park Restaurant Planning Committee, Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Liquor license application, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Square Dance, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - SVEP, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Valentine Cabaret, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Valentine Cabaret, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Valentine Cabaret, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - 17 reel-to-reel audio tapes (1200 ft), Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 6 reel-to-reel tapes (600 ft.), Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - slides, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1 approx. in. tape, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Agendas, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - ANC Information, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Bank business and information, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Board and Commissions, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - By-laws, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - BZA, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Charitable Solicitors License, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Community based development, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - D.C. statehood, Undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Youth orchestra, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Director, Board of Directors, past and present, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Drug information, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Festival Committee, Undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Lease, Undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Liability insurance, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Maps, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Merkle press, Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - MWPHA, Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Minutes (Board mtgs.), Undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - National Neighbors, Undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - News articles, Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Newsletter, Undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - No fault insurance, Undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Office manager- job description, Undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Post office, Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Printing, Undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Project Learn, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Projects, Undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Receipt, financial, Undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Square Dance, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Telephone, Undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Project Kindle, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Awards, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Contributions for BZA proceedings, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Square Dance, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Directory of businesses, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, Board meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Nominating Committee, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Neighbors Day Street, 1982, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Open House, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - National Neighbors Annual Conf., 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - National Neighbors Annual Conf., 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - National Neighbors Annual Conf., 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - National Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - National Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - National Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - National Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - NI Area groups, Undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Neighbors Halloween, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Old Membership cards, letters and ad rates, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Personnel manual, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Police crime prevention printouts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Planning, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Postal regulations, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Programs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Program planning, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Proposed org. or Neighbors Inc., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Real estate, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Resident complaints, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Social services, Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Volunteer lists, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Ward 5 information, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Whistle Stop, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - By-laws committee, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Advertising newsletters, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Valentine Caberets, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Burn out information, Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Citizens Planning Coalition, Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Economic Revitalization, Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - D.C. Fed. Civic Association Member Lists, Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Education, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Encampment for Citizenship, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - FY 1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - History meeting, 29796 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Historic preservation, Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - House and Garden tour, Undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Housing articles, Undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Housing Committee, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Ink contracts and information, Undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Jr. Neighbors, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jr. Neighbors, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jr. Neighbors, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Jr. Neighbors, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Jr. Neighbors, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Letter for outgoing and incoming, Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Letter for outgoing and incoming, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Area organizations, Undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Minutes from Board meetings, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Bylaws (revised and original copies) original 1966 and amended 1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Articles of Incorporation (original and copies), Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Waterline lawsuit, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Silver Spring Blueprint bills, Undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Rudden, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Yeta appeal, Undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Day book journal of income and deposits, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - State and federal tax returns, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Membership Thank you letters, Undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Membership lists, Undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Brightwood, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Manor Park, Undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Shepherd, Undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Takoma, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Out of area Members, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Forms for Membership, Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Membership summary reports, 1960-1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - National Savings and Trust Co., Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Independent Federal SandL Corresp., Undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Instructions for canvassing, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer reports, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer reports, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer reports, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Budget FY 74-76, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Residential permit parking litigation, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Residential permit parking petition, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Social Activities Committee, Undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Schafft Study, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Statehood, Undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Takoma, Undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Takoma, Undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Theater subscription, Undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Transportation and parking, Undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - United National Association of the USA, Capital area division, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - WMATA agreement for use and occupancy, Undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - 1975 Newcomers open house, Undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - N.W. Boundary Civic Assn. newsletter, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Plan Takoma, Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Plan Takoma, Undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Walter Reed, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Walter Reed, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Public Interest Research Group, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Youth Orchestra, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Can't Tear It Down, Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Education, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Football Weekend, December 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Foster Homes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Georgia Avenue Businessmen, Undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - General membership meeting, 28295 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - General, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Awards and Commendations, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Group Homes (Rabbi Bogner), Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - House and Garden Tour, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Housing and Community Development Policies Statement, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Housing Inspection Project, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - IED, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Job Co-op, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Junior Neighbors, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Librarian Study, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lusk List Invitees to Welcome Party, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Metro stops Feeder buses, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Metrorail, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - NAHRO, Undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Multiracial neighborhood Organization, Undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - National Capital Planning Commission, Undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - National Neighbors, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - National Neighbors, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - National Neighbors, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - National Neighbors, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Neighborhood Preservation and National Trust, Undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Neighborhood Services Anti-iron, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Neighbors Seeking Neighbors Pamphlet, Undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - ANCs, Undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Aptech II, Inc., Undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Alternative flight patterns - National Airport, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Black drama collective, Undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Board of directors, 1971, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Cady-Lee house, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Paid bills, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Census tract data, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Advisory Cmte., Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - City Council, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Committees, City council and Black Caucus, Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Community crime prevention, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Community involvement competition, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Crime prevention, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Clarke's tax bills, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Davis Dance Center, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Curb matching grant, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - D.C. City council, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - D.C. power, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Ga. Ave. Businesses, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - LEAA grant proposal, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Merkle computer systems, Inc., Undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Minutes from board meetings, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Clippings and articles, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - President, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Safeway expansion issue, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Rhodes Tavern, Undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Annual and general membership meetings, 1967-1971 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Annual and general membership meetings, 1967-1971 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Annual and general membership meetings, 1967-1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Annual and general membership meetings, 1967-1971 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Constitution By-Laws and Articles of Incorp. Neighbors, Undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Surveys and statistics, Undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Constitution: By-laws, Undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Board Correspondence, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Committee Director, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Board Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Board Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Water Line Correspondence, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Robert Williamson, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Ward 4 Summary profile - draft, 27791 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Volunteers, Undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Water Line case, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Welcome books, Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - West Mount Airy Neighbors, Undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Three Sisters Bridge, Undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Washington Center for Metro Studies, Undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Transportation, Undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Misc. associations, Undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Missouri Commission on Human Rights, Undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - MOCO Jr. College, Undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - National Assn. of Housing and Redevelop., Undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Natl. Assn. of Social Workers, Undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Natl. Civil Liberties Clearinghouse, Undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - National Conf. of Christians and Jews, Undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - National Capital Planning Commission, Undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - NW Family Centers, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 32)